[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Aishah RA said that the character of the Prophet Muhammad SAW resembled",
        "answers": [
            "The Quran",
            "The Angels",
            "His Parents"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The Quran",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which hand did Prophet Muhammad SAW say we should use for all good things?",
        "answers": [
            "Right Hand",
            "Left Hand",
            "Neither"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Right Hand",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said \"He who does not show _ to our young ones is not one of us.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Love",
            "Mercy",
            "Truth"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mercy",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said \"He who does not _ our elders is not one of us.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Love",
            "Respect",
            "Care for"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Respect",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "MA"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "It is Sunnah to eat and drink while",
        "answers": [
            "Standing",
            "Jogging",
            "Sitting"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sitting",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What should be our intention when doing any good deed?",
        "answers": [
            "To be famous",
            "To please others",
            "To please Allah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "To please Allah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "On which side is it sunnah to sleep on?",
        "answers": [
            "The right side",
            "The left side",
            "Your back"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The right side",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What would Prophet Muhammad SAW say to thank people?",
        "answers": [
            "Al Hamdulilah",
            "Jazak Allah Khayr",
            "Shukran"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Jazak Allah Khayr",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "If you do not have anything nice to say, what should you do?",
        "answers": [
            "Say a nice lie",
            "Say what's on your mind",
            "Remain Silent"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Remain Silent",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What should you say before doing anything?",
        "answers": [
            "Seek Refuge from the Shaytan",
            "Bismillah",
            "Make Du'a"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bismillah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "What must you say when you sneeze?",
        "answers": [
            "Al Hamdulilah",
            "Bismillah",
            "Apologize"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Al Hamdulilah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said \"_ is part of faith.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Happiness",
            "Cleanliness",
            "Love"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cleanliness",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "\"Beware of _, because it destroys good deeds like how fire destroys wood\"",
        "answers": [
            "Jealousy",
            "Backbiting",
            "Stealing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Jealousy",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SD"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Which body part did Prophet Muhammad SAW say causes the most sins?",
        "answers": [
            "Private Parts",
            "The Tongue",
            "The Hands"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The Tongue",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which day of the week is it sunnah to have an islamic bath?",
        "answers": [
            "Sunday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Friday",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Which foot should you exit the toilet with? ",
        "answers": [
            "Right Foot",
            "Left Foot",
            "Both"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Right Foot",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Which hand should you use when cleaning yourself in the toilet?",
        "answers": [
            "Right Hand",
            "Left Hand",
            "Both"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Left Hand",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "How tall was the Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Tall",
            "Short",
            "Medium Height"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Medium Height",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What did Prophet Muhammad SAW use to brush his teeth?",
        "answers": [
            "Miswak",
            "Toothbrush",
            "Electric Toothbrush"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Miswak",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What colour was the hair of the Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Brown",
            "Blonde",
            "Black"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Black",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What colour was Prophet Muhammad's SAW eyes?",
        "answers": [
            "Hazel",
            "Blue",
            "Black"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Black",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "How did Prophet Muhammad SAW keep his moustache?",
        "answers": [
            "Trimmed",
            "Shaved",
            "Grown"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Trimmed",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Which fruit did Prophet Muhammad SAW eat most often?",
        "answers": [
            "Figs",
            "Dates",
            "Grapes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Dates",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What does the word Adab mean?",
        "answers": [
            "Good Manners",
            "Heart",
            "The Last Day"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Good Manners",
        "topic": "A",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Who said the following \"We found it difficult to keep pace when we walked with him, and he walked at his normal pace\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Salman Al Farisi",
            "Abu Hurayrah",
            "Zaid ibn Harithah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Hurayrah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "\"Do not eat with the left hand because _ eat with the left hand\"",
        "answers": [
            "Jinns",
            "Shayatin",
            "Kufar"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Shayatin",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "\"Whoever _ us is not one of us\"",
        "answers": [
            "Cheats",
            "Fights",
            "Tortures"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cheats",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Who described the face of Prophet Muhammad SAW as, \"It was as if the brightness of the sun had shone from his auspicious face\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Khadijah",
            "Abu Hurayrah",
            "Zaid ibn Harithah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Hurayrah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "When do you use \"Oh Allah, I seek your protection from the evil jinn and the evil doers\"",
        "answers": [
            "Entering the toilet",
            "Entering a place of knowledge",
            "Entering your house"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Entering the toilet",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What is the most important thing a child can do for a parent who has passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "Make Du'a for them",
            "Give charity on their behalf",
            "Bury them somewhere special"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Make Du'a for them",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "When Prophet Muhammad SAW was asked, \"What is piety?\" He replied",
        "answers": [
            "Piety is good character",
            "Piety is worshiping at all times",
            "Piety is only achieved at old age"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Piety is good character",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "\"Whoever does not show _ will not be shown mercy.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Love",
            "Mercy",
            "Cleanliness"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mercy",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW describe as having so many rights that he thought they might be given the right of inheritance?",
        "answers": [
            "Neighbours",
            "Teachers",
            "Parents"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Neighbours",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Abu Hurayrah RA said, \"Prophet Muhammad SAW had _ cheeks.",
        "answers": [
            "Smooth",
            "Round",
            "Flat"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Smooth",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Anas Ibn Malik RA described Prophet Muhammad's SAW hands as being softer than which material?",
        "answers": [
            "Cotton",
            "Silk",
            "Leather"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Silk",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Whoever does not show gratitude to the people has not shown gratitude to _\"",
        "answers": [
            "The People",
            "Allah SW",
            "Their Parents"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Allah SW",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SD"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Aishah RA said, \"Whenever Prophet Muhammad SAW was given a choice between two things, he would always choose the _ of the two, as long as it was permissible.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Harder",
            "Easier",
            "Opposite"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Easier",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "According to a famous hadith, what is the right of the sick upon you?",
        "answers": [
            "Cure Them",
            "Visit Them",
            "Give Them Presents"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Visit Them",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "According to a famous hadith, what is a person's right if they invite you over for a meal?",
        "answers": [
            "Accept The Invitation",
            "Bring Them Presents",
            "Pay For The Meal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Accept The Invitation",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "According to a famous hadith, what is the right of someone who has passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "Attend Their Funeral",
            "Pay Their Debts",
            "Forgive Their Wrongdoings"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Attend Their Funeral",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Nothing is heavier on the scale of deeds than your good _\"",
        "answers": [
            "Manners",
            "Actions",
            "Thoughts"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Manners",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"If you have good manners, you may attain the same level of piety as those who spend their nights in worship and days in  _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Itikaf",
            "Fasting",
            "Learning"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fasting",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said that two things get most people in Paradise. What are they?",
        "answers": [
            "Taqwa & Good Manners",
            "Worship & Fasting",
            "Sadaqah & Umrah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Taqwa & Good Manners",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "What seasoning was used most by Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Garlic",
            "Salt",
            "Vinegar"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Vinegar",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "How long was the hair of Prophet Muhammad SAW according to 'Aishah RA?",
        "answers": [
            "Below his ear lobes & Above his shoulders",
            "Below his shoulders",
            "Above his ear lobes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Below his ear lobes & Above his shoulders",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Jabir RA said, \"Prophet Muhammad SAW would never _ anything he was asked for.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Accept",
            "Pass On",
            "Deny"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Deny",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Regarding the speed at which Prophet Muhammad SAW walked, Abu Hurayrah RA said, \"I did not see anyone walk _ than him.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Faster",
            "At the same speed as",
            "Slower"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Faster",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "In which month of the Islamic calendar year was Prophet Muhammad SAW most generous?",
        "answers": [
            "Ramadan",
            "Shawal",
            "Rabi' Al Awal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ramadan",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "On which hand would Prophet Muhammad SAW wear his ring?",
        "answers": [
            "Right Hand",
            "Left Hand",
            "He Had No Rings"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Right Hand",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "In regards to Prophet Muhammad's SAW bravery, who said that he was always at the front of the battlefield closest to the enemy?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Abu Hurayrah",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "What did Prophet Muhammad SAW use to do before sleeping?",
        "answers": [
            "Perform Wudhu",
            "Give Sadaqah",
            "Perform Umrah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Perform Wudhu",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "What surahs did Prophet Muhammad SAW use to recite before sleeping?",
        "answers": [
            "Surah Al Baqarah & Surah Ali Imran",
            "Surah Al Fil & Surah Al Rahman",
            "Surah Al Mulk & Surah As Sajdah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Surah Al Mulk & Surah As Sajdah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "AM"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "Which verse of the Qur'an did Prophet Muhammad SAW recommend we recite before sleeping every night?",
        "answers": [
            "First 10 Ayahs of Al Kahf",
            "Ayat Al Kursi",
            "Last Ayah of Al Baqarah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ayat Al Kursi",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said three times, \"By Allah, he is not a believer!\" When he was asked who he is referring to, he responded \"The one whose _ is not safe from his harm.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Neighbour",
            "Teacher",
            "Parents"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Neighbour",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "\"None of you truly believe until he loves for his _ what he loves for himself.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Father",
            "Neighbour",
            "Brother"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Brother",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "When a man asked Prophet Muhammad SAW for advice, what did the Prophet SAW advice him three times?",
        "answers": [
            "Give Charity",
            "Don't Get Angry",
            "Perform Salah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Don't Get Angry",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "\"The strong person isn't the one who wins the wrestling match, but the strong person is the one who controls himself when he is _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Angry",
            "Excited",
            "Sad"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Angry",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"He is not a believer, he who eats to his fill whilst his _ goes hungry.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Brother",
            "Father",
            "Neighbour"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Neighbour",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "When making du'a, what is the sunnah number of times to repeat a dua?",
        "answers": [
            "Three times",
            "Five times",
            "Once"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Three times",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"None of you truly believe until I become more beloved to him, than his children, his _, and all people.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Father",
            "Neighbour",
            "Brother"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Father",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "Allah SW says, \"Indeed, you are on the highest standard of character.\" Who is this referring to?",
        "answers": [
            "Prophet Muhammad SAW",
            "Prophet 'Isa AS",
            "Prophet Musa AS"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Prophet Muhammad SAW",
        "topic": "Q",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "Surah Al Qalam 68:4"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "What would Prophet Muhammad SAW do when he would hear a baby cry in the mosque?",
        "answers": [
            "Shorten the Salah",
            "Pause the Salah",
            "Stop the Salah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Shorten the Salah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Hastiness is from _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "The Shaytan",
            "Your Neighbour",
            "Al Masih Ad Dajjal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The Shaytan",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "Which direction is it Sunnah to face when making du'a?",
        "answers": [
            "Al Ka'bah",
            "Al Quds",
            "Madinah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Al Ka'bah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Whoever conceals the _ of a Muslim, Allah will conceal his _ in this life and the Hereafter.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Faults",
            "Good Deeds",
            "Hatred"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Faults",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Whosoever follows a path to seek _, Allah will make easy for him a path to Paradise.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Wealth",
            "Happiness",
            "Knowledge"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Knowledge",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"The one who cares for  _, Him and myself will be together in Paradise like this,\" and he held his two fingers together to illustrate.",
        "answers": [
            "An Elderly",
            "An Orphan",
            "A Neighbour"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "An Orphan",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Guard yourself from the Hellfire even with half a _ in charity. If he cannot find it, then with a kind word.",
        "answers": [
            "Date",
            "Coffee",
            "Meal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Date",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW discouraged fasting while _.",
        "answers": [
            "Working",
            "Travelling",
            "Performing Umrah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Travelling",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"The parable of what Allah sent me with, in terms of guidance and knowledge, is like the parable of _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Rain",
            "Sunrise",
            "Hail"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Rain",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad's SAW reply when he was asked why he prayed so much even though all his mistakes were forgiven was \"Should I not be a _ servant\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Grateful",
            "Humble",
            "Loving"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Grateful",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "Which two days of the week was Prophet Muhammad SAW in the habit of fasting on?",
        "answers": [
            "Monday & Tuesday",
            "Monday & Thursday",
            "Friday & Sunday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Monday & Thursday",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "Allah SW says, \"O Prophet, definitely we have sent you as a witness, a bearer of glad tidings, and a _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Warner",
            "Destroyer",
            "Soldier"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Warner",
        "topic": "Q",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "Surah Al Ahzab 33:45"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "What two qualities did Prophet Muhammad SAW say caused Barakah (blessings) in a sale?",
        "answers": [
            "Cheating & Lying",
            "Truthfulness & Clarity",
            "Humbleness & Truthfulness"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Truthfulness & Clarity",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "Who said this: \"Shyness dose not bring anything except good\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Prophet Muhammad SAW",
            "Prophet 'Isa AS",
            "Prophet Ya'qub AS"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Prophet Muhammad SAW",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "What did Prophet Muhammad SAW refer to as the lowest branch of faith?",
        "answers": [
            "Removing an obstacle from the road",
            "Fighter your inner desires",
            "Spreading positivity"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Removing an obstacle from the road",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "Who described the Prophet Muhammed SAW as, \"He is more generous at giving charity than the blowing wind\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas",
            "Abu Hurayrah",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"A good word is _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Halal",
            "Charity",
            "Happiness"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Charity",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "What did 'Aishah RA describe Prophet Muhammad's SAW laugh as being?",
        "answers": [
            "Loud",
            "Quiet",
            "Just a smile"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Just a smile",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "Which hand would Prophet Muhammad SAW comb his hair with?",
        "answers": [
            "Right Hand",
            "Left Hand",
            "Both"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Right Hand",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "Which shoe would Prophet Muhammad SAW put on first?",
        "answers": [
            "Right Shoe",
            "Left Shoe",
            "Both at the same time"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Right Shoe",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "Regarding the modesty of Prophet Muhammad SAW, Abu Sa'id Al Khudri RA said he was more shy than what?",
        "answers": [
            "An Infant",
            "An unmarried young girl",
            "The wives of the sahabah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "An unmarried young girl",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Verily, the best of you are those with the best _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Homes",
            "Character",
            "Marketing Skills"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Character",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "What was the handle of Prophet Muhammad's SAW sword made from?",
        "answers": [
            "Leather",
            "Gold",
            "Silver"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Silver",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "What colour turban did Prophet Muhammad SAW often wear?",
        "answers": [
            "White",
            "Black",
            "Grey"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Black",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammed SAW said, \"Verily, I was not sent to invoke curses, but rather I was only sent as _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Mercy",
            "Joy",
            "Hope"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mercy",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "How many Rak'ahs of Qiyam Al Layl (late night prayer) would Prophet Muhammad SAW usually pray?",
        "answers": [
            "Eleven",
            "Twelve",
            "Ten"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eleven",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "Who narrated that Prophet Muhammad SAW would repair his own shoes?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Umayr",
            "Umm Salamah",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Aishah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "Which child did Prophet Muhammad SAW visit when the child's pet died?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Umayr",
            "Salman Al Farisi",
            "Anas Ibn Malik"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Umayr",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": " Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"If the son of Adam had two valleys of money, he would wish for a third, for nothing fills the belly of the son of Adam except _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Halal Food",
            "Dust",
            "Death"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Dust",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "Who described Prophet Muhammad SAW as, \"He is well spoken, clear in what he says, saying neither too much nor too little.\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Salamah",
            "Umm Ma'bad",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Ma'bad",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "AM"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "Regarding how Prophet Muhammad SAW lowered his gaze, he was described as, \"He would look at the ground more than the _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Sky",
            "Eyes",
            "Horizon"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sky",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": " Prophet Muhammad SAW was described as, \"He has companions who surround him. If he speaks they listen to him, and if he commands, they rush to _ him.",
        "answers": [
            "Hug",
            "Obey",
            "Deny"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Obey",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "AM"
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "Who narrated that Prophet Muhammad SAW would sow and patch his own clothes?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah",
            "'Abdullah Ibn Ja'ffar",
            "Mus'ab Ibn Sa'd"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Aishah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "Who described Prophet Muhammad SAW as, \"His sweat smealt nicer than the best perfume\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Sulaym",
            "'Aishah",
            "Umm Salamah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Sulaym",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "Aishah said that sometimes there would be nothing to eat in the house except two black things. What was she referring to?",
        "answers": [
            "Water & Dates",
            "Chocolate & Dates",
            "Dates & Blackberries"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Water & Dates",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Verily, Allah is generous and he loves generosity and good _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Character",
            "Charity",
            "Food"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Character",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SK"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW discouraged people from coming to the mosque with bad _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Smelly armpits",
            "Breathe",
            "Humour"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Breathe",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"It's not part of righteousness to _ while on a journey.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Fight",
            "Fast",
            "Give Charity"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fast",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "How many straps did Prophet Muhammad's shoes have?",
        "answers": [
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "One"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Two",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "When the people of Ta'if threw stones at Prophet Muhammad SAW what dua did he make?",
        "answers": [
            "Forgive my people for they know not",
            "May they be destroyed",
            "May they burn in hell"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Forgive my people for they know not",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "When Prophet Muhammad SAW was asked if he told jokes, what did he reply?",
        "answers": [
            "Yes but I always speak the truth",
            "No joking is haram",
            "No I never speak lies"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Yes but I always speak the truth",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "When Jabir RA was describing the Prophet Muhammad SAW he said, \"He was more handsome than the _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Full Moon",
            "Bright Sun",
            "Glistening Gold"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Full Moon",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "\"Prophet Muhammad SAW would not abuse others, he would not use vulgar words, and he would not curse others.\" Who narrates this hadith?",
        "answers": [
            "Anas Ibn Malik",
            "'Aishah",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Anas Ibn Malik",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "What was Prophet Muhammad's SAW ring made from?",
        "answers": [
            "Silver",
            "Gold",
            "Platinum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Silver",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "Where was the gemstone on Prophet Muhammad's ring from?",
        "answers": [
            "Abyssinia",
            "Persia",
            "Jerusalem"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abyssinia",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "What would Prophet Muhammad SAW use his ring for?",
        "answers": [
            "Salute companions",
            "As a seal to stamp letters",
            "Proof that he is a prophet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "As a seal to stamp letters",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "What was written on Prophet Muhammad's official seal?",
        "answers": [
            "Muhammad The Messenger of Allah",
            "Muhammad The Slave of Allah",
            "Muhammad The Ruler of Islam"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Muhammad The Slave of Allah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "Which woman met Prophet Muhammad SAW during his Hijrah and gave a detailed description of him?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Ma'bad",
            "Umm Salamah",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Ma'bad",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "When did Prophet Muhammad SAW ever pray sitting down?",
        "answers": [
            "During his final illness",
            "While injured in battles",
            "While travelling to Madinah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "During his final illness",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW was described by a companion as, \"His ideas were _ moving on their strings.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Pearls",
            "Gold",
            "Light"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pearls",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "AM"
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "Who described Prophet Muhammad SAW as follows, \"I saw a man who is handsome, of glowing countenance, and of good proportions, with neither a large stomach nor a small head\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Ma'bad",
            "'Aishah",
            "Bilal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Ma'bad",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "AM"
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "Who described the Prophet Muhammed SAW as, \"He maintained family ties, helped the weak, helped the poor, was generous to guests and patient with hardship\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Khadijah",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "Zaid ibn Harithah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Khadijah",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "Abu Juhayfah said about Prophet Muhammad's SAW hands, \"It was colder than ice and better smelling than _.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Jasmine",
            "Musk",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Musk",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "To what did Prophet Muhammad SAW compare a person who takes back his or her gifts?",
        "answers": [
            "A dog who licks its own vomit",
            "A dog who licks its own nose",
            "A cat who licks itself clean"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A dog who licks its own vomit",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB & SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "Which companion narrated that Prophet Muhammad SAW cried when he recited Qur'an for the Prophet SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah Ibn Mas'ud",
            "'Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas",
            "Abu Hurayrah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdullah Ibn Mas'ud",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "What did Prophet Muhammad SAW do when he learnt that a woman attempted to poison him?",
        "answers": [
            "He exiled her",
            "He forgave her",
            "He executed her"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "He forgave her",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW said, \"Whatever a man spends on his family intending Allah's pleasure is considered as _ for him.\"",
        "answers": [
            "Charity",
            "Wealth",
            "Obligatory"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Charity",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW say we should prioritize spending our money on?",
        "answers": [
            "Friends",
            "Dependents",
            "The Poor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Dependents",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SB"
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "Where was the seal of prophethood located?",
        "answers": [
            "Between his shoulders",
            "On his chest",
            "On his arm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Between his shoulders",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "SM"
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW say this to, \"My son, greet your family when you enter your home, for that is a blessing for you and your family\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Anas Ibn Malik",
            "Zaid Ibn Harithah",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Anas Ibn Malik",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "ST"
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "Who was the first rightly guided Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "Who was the second rightly guided Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "Who was the third rightly guided Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "Who was the fourth rightly guided Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "How many daughters did Prophet Muhammad SAW have?",
        "answers": [
            "Four",
            "Five",
            "Six"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Four",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "How many sons did Prophet Muhammad SAW have?",
        "answers": [
            "Three",
            "Four",
            "Five"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Three",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "Who was the first wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah",
            "Khadijah",
            "Sawda"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Khadijah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "What title was given to the wives of the Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Mothers of the Believers",
            "Wives of Muhammad",
            "Wives of the Prophet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mothers of the Believers",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "Who were the two grandsons of Prophet Muhammad SAW whose mother was Fatimah?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan & Hussayn",
            "Ahmad & Mahmoud",
            "Khaled & 'Amr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hassan & Hussayn",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "Who was the father of Hassan?",
        "answers": [
            "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "Which uncle of Prophet Muhammad SAW was known as the 'Lion of Allah'?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamzah",
            "Abu Talib",
            "Abu Lahab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hamzah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "How many children did Prophet Muhammad SAW have?",
        "answers": [
            "Seven",
            "Six",
            "Eight"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Seven",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "What was the name of Prophet Muhammad's SAW grandfather?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdul Muttalib",
            "Abu Talib",
            "'Abdullah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdul Muttalib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "Who took care of Prophet Muhammad SAW after his grandfather passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Talib",
            "Hamzah",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "Who was the father of Hussayn?",
        "answers": [
            "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "Who was the second daughter of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruqayyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "What is the arabic word used to refer to the family of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Ahlul Bayt",
            "Ahlul Rasul",
            "Baytul Rasul"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ahlul Bayt",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "Which companion married two of Prophet Muhammad's SAW daughters?",
        "answers": [
            "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "When asked by 'Amr Ibn Al 'Aas whom he loved the most, Prophet Muhammad SAW responded with?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah Bint Abi Bakr",
            "Khadijah Bint Khuwaylid",
            "Sawda Bint Zam'a"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Aishah Bint Abi Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "Who was the second son of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah",
            "Qasim",
            "Ibrahim"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdullah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "Who was the firstborn child of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah",
            "Qasim",
            "Ibrahim"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Qasim",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "Who was the eldest daughter of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "Who was the last of Prophet Muhammad's SAW children to pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Ibrahim",
            "Fatimah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fatimah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "From which daughter does the lineage of Prophet Muhammad SAW continue through?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fatimah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "Who was Fatimah Bint Muhammad married to?",
        "answers": [
            "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
            "Salman Al Farisi"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "Which son of Abu Talib was raised in Prophet Muhammad's SAW house?",
        "answers": [
            "Ja'far",
            "'Ali",
            "Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Ali",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "Which freed slave chose Prophet Muhammad SAW over their own father?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaid",
            "Bilal",
            "Sumayyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaid",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "Who was the father of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Ahmad",
            "'Abdullah",
            "Ibrahim"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Abdullah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "Who was the mother of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Aminah",
            "Zaynab",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Aminah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "At what age was Prophet Muhammad SAW when his father passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "At the age of 2",
            "At the age of 5",
            "Before he was born"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Before he was born",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "Who was the mother of 'Ali Ibn Abi Talib?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah",
            "'Aishah",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fatimah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "Which uncle of Prophet Muhammad SAW was taken prisoner at the Battle of Badr?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamzah",
            "Abu Talib",
            "'Abbas"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Abbas",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "Which of the four Caliphs died a natural death?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad SAW led an army?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah",
            "'Aishah",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Aishah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was married to him through the Qur'an?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah",
            "Zaynab",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "Which wife did Prophet Muhammad SAW marry after the conquest of Khaybar?",
        "answers": [
            "Safiyyah",
            "Zaynab",
            "Fatimah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Safiyyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "Prophet Muhammad SAW had a dream that he should marry which of his wives?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah",
            "'Aishah",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Aishah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was not previously married?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Safiyya"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Aishah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "Who was the fourth woman that Prophet Muhammad SAW married?",
        "answers": [
            "Hafsah",
            "Safiyya",
            "Sawda"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hafsah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "Which grandson of Prophet Muhammad SAW was martyred at Karbala?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan",
            "Hussayn",
            "'Ali"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hussayn",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW prophecize would make peace between two Muslim groups?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan",
            "Hussayn",
            "'Ali"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hassan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "Who ordered for the Qur'an to be compiled and bounded into one volume?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "Which Caliph standardized the Qur'an and had copies distributed across the Muslim nation?",
        "answers": [
            "Uthman",
            "'Ali",
            "'Umar"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Uthman",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "Who was the last son of Prophet Muhammad SAW to pass away? ",
        "answers": [
            "Ibrahim",
            "Qasim",
            "'Abdullah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ibrahim",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "Which companion was considered the most modest, even the angels felt shy in front of him?",
        "answers": [
            "Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
            "Abu Bakr As Siddiq",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "Which daughter of Prophet Muhammad made Hijrah to Abyssinia with 'Uthman Ibn 'Affan?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruqayyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": " Which companion was considered as Prophet Muhammad's SAW closest friend?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "How many of Prophet Muhammad's SAW wives passed away during his lifetime?",
        "answers": [
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "One"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Two",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "What was the name of Zayd Ibn Harithah's son that Prophet Muhammad SAW treated like his own grandson?",
        "answers": [
            "Muhsin",
            "'Ali",
            "Usamah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Usamah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "How many of Prophet Muhammad's SAW wives were still alive when he passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "Nine",
            "Seven",
            "Eleven"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Nine",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "Which son of Abu Bakr assisted him during the Hijrah?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah",
            "'Abdul Rahman",
            "Muhammad"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdullah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "Which daughter of Prophet Muhammad SAW was the first to pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Umm Kulthum",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruqayyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": " Which son of Prophet Muhammad SAW was the first to pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Ibrahim",
            "Qasim",
            "'Abdullah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Qasim",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "Who was the first wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW to pass away after him?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab",
            "'Aishah",
            "Hafsah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "Which daughter of 'Umar Ibn Al Khattab was married to Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah",
            "Hafsah",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hafsah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "Which daughter of Abu Bakr was married to Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Asma",
            "Umm Kulthum",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Aishah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW marry first after Khadijah?",
        "answers": [
            "Aishah",
            "Sawda",
            "Zaynab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sawda",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad SAW became the custodian of the Qur'an?",
        "answers": [
            "Hafsah",
            "Zaynab",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hafsah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "question": "How was 'Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas related to Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Cousins",
            "Brothers",
            "Uncle & Nephew"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cousins",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "Who ordered his sons to break their engagement with Prophet Muhammad's SAW daughters?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Jahl",
            "Abu Lahab",
            "Abu Bakr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Lahab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "Which two wives of Prophet Muhammad SAW was Surah At-Tahrim revealed about?",
        "answers": [
            "Hafsah & 'Aishah",
            "'Aishah & Zaynab",
            "Umm Salamah & Umm Habibah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hafsah & 'Aishah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "question": "In which year after Hijrah did Prophet Muhammad's SAW daughter Umm Kulthum pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "9th Year",
            "10th Year",
            "11th Year"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "9th Year",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "question": "By what name was Prophet Muhammad's SAW great grandson 'Ali Ibn Hussayn more popularly known as?",
        "answers": [
            "Zayn Al 'Abidin",
            "Khaled Ibn Al Walid",
            "Zayd Al Mustajibin"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zayn Al 'Abidin",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "question": "During the reign of which Caliph did Hassan Ibn 'Ali pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Mu'awiyah Ibn Abi Sufyan",
            "Yazid Ibn Mu'awiyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mu'awiyah Ibn Abi Sufyan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "During the reign of which Caliph did Hussayn Ibn 'Ali pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Mu'awiyah Ibn Abi Sufyan",
            "Yazid Ibn Mu'awiyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Yazid Ibn Mu'awiyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "question": "During the reign of which Caliph did 'Aishah Bint Abi Bakr pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "Mu'awiyah Ibn Abi Sufyan",
            "Yazid Ibn Mu'awiyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mu'awiyah Ibn Abi Sufyan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the wars of apostasy take place?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "Abu Bakr As-Siddiq"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr As-Siddiq",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the first civil war take place?",
        "answers": [
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
            "Abu Bakr As-Siddiq"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "question": "Around the time of which battle did Ruqayyah pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Battle of Badr",
            "Battle of Uhud",
            "Battle of the Trench"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Battle of Badr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "question": "Who was the father of Prophet Muhammad's SAW great granddaughter Fatimah As-Saghrah?",
        "answers": [
            "Hussayn",
            "Hassan",
            "'Ali"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hussayn",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "question": "Which companion immediately believed the story of Al 'Israh & Mi'raj upon hearing it?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "Bilal",
            "'Umar"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "question": "Who was the cousin of Prophet Muhammad SAW who became a famous hadith and tafsir scholar?",
        "answers": [
            "Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas",
            "Ja'far Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abdullah Ibn 'Abbas",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "question": "Who was the mother of 'Aishah Bint Abi Bakr?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Ruman",
            "Fatimah",
            "Safiyyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Ruman",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "question": "Who was the mother of Hafsah Bint 'Umar?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab Bint Madhun",
            "Zaynab Bint Jahsh",
            "Zaynab Bint Khuzayma"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab Bint Madhun",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "question": "Which wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW was of Jewish origin?",
        "answers": [
            "Safiyyah Bint Huyayy",
            "Sawda Bint Zam'a",
            "Zaynab Bint Jahsh"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Safiyyah Bint Huyayy",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "question": "Who did the people of Iraq choose as Caliph after 'Ali passed away?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan",
            "Hussayn",
            "'Abdullah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hassan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "question": "Which famous dynasty were the descendants of one of the uncles of Prophet Muhammad SAW?",
        "answers": [
            "Umayyad",
            "Abbasid",
            "Ottoman"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abbasid",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "question": "What were the family of Prophet Muhammad SAW prohibited from taking?",
        "answers": [
            "Gifts",
            "Charity",
            "Advice"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Charity",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "question": "How many times has the name Muhammad been mentioned in the Qur'an?",
        "answers": [
            "Four",
            "Five",
            "Six"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Four",
        "topic": "Q",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "question": "At the time of the death of Prophet Muhammad SAW, how many memorizers of the Qur'an were there?",
        "answers": [
            "Twenty Two",
            "Nineteen",
            "Twelve"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Twenty Two",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "question": "Who is the only woman to be mentioned by name in the Qur'an?",
        "answers": [
            "Maryam",
            "'Aishah",
            "Khadijah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Maryam",
        "topic": "Q",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "question": "Which Prophet is mentioned most in the Qur'an?",
        "answers": [
            "Musa",
            "'Eisa (Jesus)",
            "Muhammad"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Musa",
        "topic": "Q",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "question": "Where is the Ka'bah located?",
        "answers": [
            "Makkah",
            "Madinah",
            "Jerusalem"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Makkah",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "question": "What are the first ten days of Ramadan called?",
        "answers": [
            "Ten days of Mercy",
            "Ten days of Forgiveness",
            "Ten days of Locked Hellfire Doors"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ten days of Mercy",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "question": "What lesson did all the Prophets of Allah teach?",
        "answers": [
            "Oneness of God",
            "Follow your desires",
            "Brotherhood"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Oneness of God",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "question": "How did 'Umar Ibn Al Khattab pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Stabbed during prayer",
            "Stabbed in the marketplace",
            "Stabbed while travelling"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Stabbed during prayer",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "question": "How did 'Uthman Ibn 'Affan pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Attacked in his home",
            "Attacked during prayer",
            "Attacked while travelling"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Attacked in his home",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "question": "What was the age difference between Prophet Muhammad SAW & his uncle 'Abbas?",
        "answers": [
            "Three Years",
            "Four Years",
            "Seven Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Three Years",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "question": "How did 'Ali Ibn Abi Talib pass away?",
        "answers": [
            "Assassinated while walking to the masjid",
            "Assassinated in his home",
            "Assassinated in the marketplace"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Assassinated while walking to the masjid",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "question": "How many years did 'Umar Ibn Al Khattab serve as Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Ten Years",
            "Five Years",
            "Seven Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ten Years",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "question": "How many years did 'Uthman serve as Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Twelve Years",
            "Ten Years",
            "Seven Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Twelve Years",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "question": "How many years did 'Ali serve as Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "4 Years",
            "4.5 Years",
            "5.5 Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "4.5 Years",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "question": "How many years did Hassan Ibn 'Ali serve as a Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Six Months",
            "Eight Months",
            "Four Months"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Six Months",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the Muslims conquer Egypt?",
        "answers": [
            "Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the first Muslim navy sail out?",
        "answers": [
            "Umar Ibn Al Khattab",
            "'Ali Ibn Abi Talib",
            "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Uthman Ibn 'Affan",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "question": "What is the name of the battle that took place between the armies of 'Ali and Mu'awiyah?",
        "answers": [
            "Battle of Siffin",
            "Battle of Uhud",
            "Battle of Nahrawan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Battle of Siffin",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the companions defeat Musaylimah Al Khadhab?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr",
            "'Ali",
            "'Uthman"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "question": "Which of the daughters of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was initially married to Utaybah Ibn Abi Lahab?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab",
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Umm Kulthum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Kulthum",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "question": "What is the name of the battle that took place between the armies of 'Ali and 'Aishah?",
        "answers": [
            "Battle of the Camel",
            "Battle of the Trench",
            "Battle of Badr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Battle of the Camel",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "question": "Which of Prophet Muhammad's SAW descendants held the position of Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan Ibn 'Ali",
            "'Hussayn Ibn 'Ali",
            "Ibrahim Ibn Muhammad"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hassan Ibn 'Ali",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "question": "In which month of the Islamic calendar was 'Uthman Ibn 'Affan martyred?",
        "answers": [
            "Dhul Hijjah",
            "Muharram",
            "Ramadan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Dhul Hijjah",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "question": "What two acts of worship was 'Uthman Ibn 'Affan doing when he was martyred?",
        "answers": [
            "Tawaf and Qur'an",
            "Fasting and Qur'an",
            "Praying and Fasting"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fasting and Qur'an",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "question": "In which month of the Islamic calendar was 'Ali Ibn Abi Talib martyred?",
        "answers": [
            "Ramadan",
            "Shawal",
            "Rabi' Al Awal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ramadan",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "question": "Which daughters of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was married to Abul 'Aas?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab",
            "Fatimah",
            "Ruqayyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "question": "Which wife of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was previously married to Zayd Ibn Harithah?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Salamah",
            "Umm Ma'bad",
            "Zaynab Bint Jahsh"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab Bint Jahsh",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "question": "Which daughter of the Prophet Muhammad SAW was initially married to 'Utbah Ibn Abu Lahab?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Zaynab",
            "Umm Kulthum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruqayyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "question": "Who performed the nikkah between Prophet Muhammad SAW and Umm Habibah?",
        "answers": [
            "King Najashi",
            "Abu Sufyan",
            "Ja'far Ibn Abi Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "King Najashi",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "question": "When did Prophet Muhammad's SAW uncle 'Abbas convert to Islam?",
        "answers": [
            "Conquest of Makkah",
            "Battle of Uhud",
            "Battle of Hunayn"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Conquest of Makkah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "question": "Initially, who did Prophet Muhammad SAW ask Zaynab Bint Jahsh to marry?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaid Ibn Harithah",
            "Bilal Ibn Rabah",
            "Salman Al Farisi"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaid Ibn Harithah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "question": "Which wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW was married to him while she was living in Abysinnia?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Habibah",
            "Umm Salamah",
            "Maymuna"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Habibah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 232,
        "question": "Who was the last woman that Prophet Muhammad SAW married?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Salamah",
            "Maymuna",
            "Umm Habibah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Maymuna",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW refer to as the leaders of the youth of Paradise?",
        "answers": [
            "Hassan & Hussayn",
            "Ahmad & Mahmoud",
            "Khaled & 'Amr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hassan & Hussayn",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 234,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW refer to as the leaders of the elders who go to Paradise?",
        "answers": [
            "Abu Bakr & 'Umar",
            "'Ali & 'Uthman",
            "Khadijah & 'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Bakr & 'Umar",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 235,
        "question": "Who did Prophet Muhammad SAW refer to as the leader of the women in Paradise?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah Bint Muhammad",
            "Khadijah",
            "'Aishah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fatimah Bint Muhammad",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 236,
        "question": "Which two uncles of Prophet Muhammad SAW converted to Islam?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamzah & 'Abbas",
            "Abu Lahab & Abu Talib",
            "Qasim & Ibrahim"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hamzah & 'Abbas",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 237,
        "question": "Which two uncles of Prophet Muhammad SAW died as pagans?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamzah & 'Abbas",
            "Abu Lahab & Abu Talib",
            "Al Harith & Az Zubayr"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abu Lahab & Abu Talib",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 238,
        "question": "At whose death was there an eclipse?",
        "answers": [
            "Ibrahim",
            "Qasim",
            "'Abdullah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ibrahim",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 239,
        "question": "Which descendant of Prophet Muhammad SAW was the teacher of Imam Abu Hanifa?",
        "answers": [
            "Imam Ja'far As Siddiq",
            "Imam Al Ghazali",
            "Imam Al Bukhari"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Imam Ja'far As Siddiq",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 240,
        "question": "In which month of the Islamic calendar was Hussayn Ibn 'Ali martyred?",
        "answers": [
            "Muharram",
            "Rabi' Al Awal",
            "Shawal"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Muharram",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 241,
        "question": "What was Umm Habibah's name?",
        "answers": [
            "Ramla",
            "Rabi'a",
            "Ruqayyah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ramla",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 242,
        "question": "During which Caliph's reign did the Muslims conquer Jerusalem?",
        "answers": [
            "Uthman",
            "'Ali",
            "'Umar"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Umar",
        "topic": "IH",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 243,
        "question": "How many years did Abu Bakr serve as Caliph?",
        "answers": [
            "2 Years",
            "2.5 Years",
            "4.5 Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2.5 Years",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 244,
        "question": "Which uncle of Prophet Muhammad SAW was in charge of the Zam Zam well and distributing its water?",
        "answers": [
            "Abbas",
            "Abu Lahab",
            "Abu Talib"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Abbas",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 245,
        "question": "Which wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW was known as the mother of the poor?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab Bint Madhun",
            "Zaynab Bint Jahsh",
            "Zaynab Bint Khuzayma"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab Bint Khuzayma",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Impossible",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 246,
        "question": "Which wife of Prophet Muhammad SAW passed away during his life in Madinah?",
        "answers": [
            "Zaynab Bint Madhun",
            "Zaynab Bint Jahsh",
            "Zaynab Bint Khuzayma"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Zaynab Bint Khuzayma",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Impossible",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 247,
        "question": "By what name was Hind Bint Abi Umayyah more commonly known as?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Salamah",
            "Umm Habibah",
            "Umm Sulaym"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Salamah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Impossible",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 248,
        "question": "What was the name of Prophet Muhammad's SAW granddaughter whose mother was Zaynab?",
        "answers": [
            "Umamah",
            "Fatimah",
            "Umm Kulthum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umamah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Impossible",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 249,
        "question": "Who was the mother of 'Abdullah Ibn 'Uthman?",
        "answers": [
            "Ruqayyah",
            "Umm Kulthum",
            "Na'ila"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ruqayyah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Impossible",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 250,
        "question": "What was the name of the wife of Abu Talib who raised Prophet Muhammad SAW after his grandfather's death?",
        "answers": [
            "Fatimah Bint Asad",
            "Fatimah Bint 'Amr",
            "Fatimah Bint Al Khattab"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fatimah Bint Asad",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 251,
        "question": "Which son of Fatimah Bint Muhammad died as a baby?",
        "answers": [
            "Muhsin",
            "Hassan",
            "Hussayn"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Muhsin",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 252,
        "question": "Which daughter of 'Ali Ibn Abi Talib married 'Umar Ibn Al Khattab?",
        "answers": [
            "Umm Kulthum",
            "Zaynab",
            "Ramla"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Umm Kulthum",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 253,
        "question": "Who was given the title 'Leader of the martyrs'?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamzah",
            "Khalid Ibn Al Walid",
            "Bilal Ibn Rabah"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hamzah",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 254,
        "question": "What was the age difference between Prophet Muhammad SAW & his uncle Hamzah?",
        "answers": [
            "Four Years",
            "Five Years",
            "Six Years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Four Years",
        "topic": "PB",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 255,
        "question": "Prophet Hud was sent to the people of?",
        "answers": [
            "Thamud",
            "'Aad",
            "Lut"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "'Aad",
        "topic": "PM",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "reference": "N/A"
    },
    {
        "id": 256,
        "question": "In which month should muslims fast?",
        "answers": [
            "Ramadan",
            "Shawal",
            "Sha'ban"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Ramadan",
        "topic": "PT",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "reference": "N/A"
    }
]
